skygarden.london 2018-05-10

# Privacy & Cookies Policy | SkyGarden

Land Securities Properties Limited (“we”, “us” or “our”) are committed to protecting the privacy of users of this website. This policy explains how we will use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website. Please read this policy carefully.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, the “data controller” for this website is Land Securities Properties Limited (company number 00961477) of 100 Victoria Street London SW1E 5JL.

### 1         HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM YOU?

1.1         We collect information about you when you sign up for our email updates, provide us with feedback, enter a promotion on our websites and/or contact us. This information may include details such as your name, email address, telephone number and any other information you provide, such as age group, interests and preferences.

1.2         We may also collect information about your use of the website using cookies.

### 2         HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

2.1         We will use the information you have provided as follows:

a)      to provide the services or information which you have requested

b)      tailor this website so the content you see is relevant to you

c)      to collect statistics, responses to any surveys and questionnaires, traffic patterns and related site information. We aggregate this data and it does not identify any website users. We use it for research, analysis, testing, monitoring, risk management and administrative purposes. Furthermore we may disclose this aggregated data to third parties for marketing, advertising or other promotional purposes.

2.2         Additionally, if you agree, we may:

a)      use the information to contact   you via social media, email or SMS  about our new developments, services and any other information we think may be of interest to you based on your use of the website

b)      pass the information on to companies within our group of companies so that they can contact  you via social media, email or SMS  with details of developments and activities which may interest you;

c)      pass the information on to other third parties so that they can contact you via social media, email or SMS  with details of developments and activities which may interest you.

2.3         We may pass on or allow access to your information:

a)      to our suppliers, contractors and professional advisors where this is necessary for them to provide services and facilities to us;

b)      to any purchaser of all or part of our business or any of our properties to which this website relates;

c)      where we are required to do so by law, court order or other legal process;

d)      where, acting in good faith, we believe disclosure is necessary to assist in the investigation or reporting of suspected illegal or other wrongful activity;

e)      to protect and defend our rights or property.

### 3         YOUR RIGHTS

3.1         You have the right to opt out of receiving any marketing information which we send you.

3.2         If you have previously consented to receiving marketing information from us and change your mind, you can withdraw your consent by emailing us at [websites@landsecurities.com](mailto:websites@landsecurities.com).

3.3         You have the right to request a copy of the personal data which we hold about you. You can request this information by contacting us at [websites@landsecurities.com](mailto:websites@landsecurities.com) . We may make a small charge for providing this information.

3.4         If you think any of the information we hold about you is out of date or incorrect, you can ask us to correct or remove this information, contact us at [websites@landsecurities.com](mailto:websites@landsecurities.com).

### 4         HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?

4.1         Cookies (and similar technologies) are small files which are sent by websites and stored on your device. They collect information about how the website is being used by those accessing it and allow websites to remember information. You can find out more about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

4.2         In our website we use cookies to collect information of how many visitors there are to different parts of the website, which helps us keep our site up to date. We may also use cookies to tailor the content that you see to suit your interests. This facility also allows you to receive personalised advertising relating to products viewed whilst using our website.

4.3         Most devices will automatically accept all cookies. However you can change your browser settings so that cookies are refused. Guidance on how to change your settings can be found at the website named above or look at the “help” menu of your device. Please be aware however that blocking cookies may hamper the website’s functionality or restrict how much of the website you can access.

4.4         For details of all the cookies which are used on our websites, their purpose, categorisation, data collected, and their persistence or expiry please see our [Cookies Usage](http://www.landsecurities.com/cookies-usage) declaration.

### 5         TRANSFERRING INFORMATION OVERSEAS

5.1         It is possible that personal data we collect from you may be transferred, stored and/or processed outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing and/or processing. You should be aware that countries outside the EEA may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom however we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### 6         LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITE

6.1         This privacy and cookies policy only applies to this website. If you link to another website from here, you should remember to read and understand that website’s privacy and cookies policy as well. We are not responsible for any use of your information that is made by other websites.

### 7         CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY & COOKIES POLICY

7.1         This policy was last updated on 27 July 2013. If it is necessary for us to alter the terms of the privacy and cookies policy, we will post the revised policy in this website.

### 8         HOW USERS CAN CONTACT US

8.1         If you have any questions about this privacy and cookies policy, please contact us at [websites@landescurities.com](mailto:websites@landescurities.com)
